<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>abhinandd.me</title>
    <link href="https://abhinandd.me/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://abhinandd.me" />
    <updated>2023-10-26T20:37:49+01:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Abhinand Dhandapani</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://abhinandd.me</id>

    <entry>
        <title>My Love ❤️ </title>
        <author>
            <name>Abhinand Dhandapani</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://abhinandd.me/my-love.html"/>
        <id>https://abhinandd.me/my-love.html</id>

        <updated>2023-10-26T20:37:49+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    <p>I recently fell in love with a girl, It was crush, trust me...</p>

                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I recently fell in love with a girl, It was crush, trust me...</p>

<p>I don't know the real meaning of love sometimes all we do is for show off and all, Sometimes things will hit differently during different times, Let call her as Tri, The all I believe is she do love me as well, I was kind of annoying person for her sometimes, I'm like enjoying every minutes spend with her.</p>
<p>For real man this was kind of amazing as the time that you spend with your loved one's are the time which you can never get back, I had thought it for alot of time what if time stood at the certain time of my life that I would be able to live with her forever without going away from her. But this is unfortunate that we are not the one who controls time something other than that is the feelings, I don't know how to express the feeling of love, But would say something like butterfly flying in your belly.</p>
<p>The impact of love on me, I previously had experience with having a girl-friend well it wasn't that serious relationship but still I loved her and told her, All she did was giving me signs of loving but it was unfortunately ended miserably, Sometimes I believe to get back with her which never happened, But always remember the first love is always the first love. I had alot of crushes on different girl during the time and after but If I feel something different in any of them I would try to make a move ahead.</p>
<p>The current condition of me, I'm planning to move into something serious but I'm not sure as I'm currently in love with a girl as I told Tri, All I want is her. I falling in love with her over everything, She gives me signs but still sometimes she changes her track, I do love her badly but I don't want her to be distracted as well this is really worst condition of me I love her alot even I just started to think about her and my future ahead, Hope everyhting goes well, I'm just fucking 22 right now and should focus more on career and not to get into anything serious until I get the fucking money I want, Yeah money is something necessary in life and easy to create and lose, I need love not to be like that.</p>
<p>I hope she feels my love she's my cutiepie I will always love her, I know it's not easy to come over a break-up, I got previous experiences with it. It's not even a month after I saw her but still I'm able to control my over-thinking where I live with her whole life in my brain. She's friendly even after knowing it, I'm really thankful for her to understand me as a friend 💔, You can never be a Lover until you yourself determine that you are ready.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
